What a waste of a good specimen.
Forget it.
We've drawn enough blood anyway.
Soon, there will be another Shen Tianbai
in Ningcheng.
Hui.
Dispose of the body.
Remember,
don't let the word out.
Yes.
What do you want me to do?
Help me take something out.
Tell me
what you want me to take.
My corpse.
[Eclipse in the Lost City] [Episode 24]
This kid is really something.
I'll have to praise him later.
Tianbai,
why are you lying here?
Why are you so cold?
It's all my fault
for letting you take on
such a dangerous mission.
Tianbai!
Officer Wu.
It's not the time to cry yet.
He left this.
Do you know what it means?
G0.
This is the serial number for the shipment
of drugs your father trafficked.
The shipment
was the first-generation version.
It should be discontinued by now.
Could it be that
the antidote lies in
fighting poison with poison?
But when the shipment was stored
in the police station warehouse,
it was destroyed.
Even if it is the antidote,
we can't find it anymore.
Tianbai clearly knew this,
so why would he—
I believe him.
If he says it's there, it must be.
If the shipment still exists,
I will definitely find it.
Could it be that
Lu Wenbiao kept a box?
[Spirit Tablet of Lu Wenbiao]
My old man prepared
a spirit tablet for himself early on.
He wasn't afraid of death.
He was afraid of dying
an unjustified death.
If he wanted to leave something
behind before he died,
it must be in...
Tianjiu Alley.
The dry well in the east.
Thirteen grids under the blue bricks.
Transporting drugs for them
is indeed the greatest mistake of my life.
It is undeniable
and unforgivable.
I don't know how to make amends.
I could only hold back one box
as a backup,
hoping that one day,
it could atone for my sins a little.
Director. Director.
Something happened in Tianjiu Alley.
I don't know what happened
to those people from before,
but the poison inside their bodies
has been completely neutralized.
What?
With the Qingtian Gang protecting them,
our men can't stop them at all.
And those from the Shisha Gang—
If the director isn't removed,
Ningcheng won't know peace!
Ningcheng is our home!
[Wolf Toxin: Westerner's Trick Bought with
Blood of Ningcheng People]
We will defend it to the death!
The police director
colluded with foreigners
and used civilians for experiments!
He is guilty of heinous crimes!
If the director isn't removed,
Ningcheng won't know peace!
Human experiments are heinous crimes!
If the director isn't removed,
Ningcheng won't know peace!
-If the director isn't removed,
-Ningcheng won't know peace!
You,
you go out first.
Okay.
Chase him.
He can't get far.
At this point,
where else can you run?
I should have settled
this score with you long ago.
Lu Ye,
I underestimated you.
I originally thought
you were like your father,
a sentimental fool
who values love and loyalty.
I didn't expect
that as long as you won,
you could sacrifice anyone,
even Shen Tianbai!
You don't deserve to mention him!
Lu Ye,
I calculated everything,
but I just couldn't read you.
There are too many things in this world
that are more important than living
and than living together.
People like you
will never understand.
You are so arrogant
that you thought
you could control everything,
but you didn't realize you were
just a lackey for the foreigners.
If you die,
there will be thousands more like you.
What's the difference
between you and Xu Qingdao?
Impossible!
How could I be like him?
You...
It's over.
It's all over.
You are quite clear-headed.
They all asked me
why I was so sure
you could bring the antidote out.
I thought to myself,
since you've decided to die,
♪ A strand of obsession ♪
what else could you not accomplish?
♪ A mortal vessel ♪
You didn't expect it, did you?
I guessed it from the very first sentence.
♪ Whose incarnation
dwells within distinct souls? ♪
Shen Tianbai.
Hello.
♪ Foes locked in strife ♪
♪ Are Incomplete in their fates ♪
When we graduated,
♪ We both refused to accept this verdict ♪
you asked me at the station
♪ Left with endless questions ♪
why I didn't say goodbye.
I said,
♪ Down the long street once more ♪
"We haven't even said hello.
♪ Lamplight traces
the curve of your profile ♪
People who haven't said hello
♪ Let wind speak for
silent pleas for vindication ♪
have no right to say goodbye."
♪ Down the long street once more ♪
Now you've said it.
Shen Tianbai,
♪ Who gently folds the past away? ♪
♪ Reality is but an illusion ♪
we really have to say goodbye now.
♪ Long has my heart been overthrown ♪
♪ I yearn for you though we stay apart ♪
♪ Our turbulent feelings
stir within our eyes ♪
♪ Love and hate collide
within a fleeting moment ♪
♪ Stirring at the very edge of memory ♪
♪ If only I could ♪
♪ Have a future with you ♪
♪ I cling tight to the past,
wishing time would hold its breath ♪
International public opinion has blown up.
The foreigners feel humiliated,
so they had to stop.
With the director dead,
this mess has been uprooted.
A large number of people
at the top have been replaced.
The antidote has been distributed
in batches.
It was a close call,
but Ningcheng is safe.
That's great.
What about you?
Have the matters
of the Shisha Gang been handled?
Xu Qingdao schemed his whole life.
He probably never calculated
that he would die so easily,
ending in total ignominy.
All of this
is his retribution.
All key positions within the Shisha Gang
are now filled by my men.
Even if some still refuse to fall in line,
they ought to see
where things stand by now.
You helped me,
so I should thank you too.
I happen to have a friend
who specializes in studying
this kind of poison.
This is his business card.
Thank you for making a special trip back.
Not at all.
Miss Xu's friend is my friend as well.
Mr. Lu,
you were right.
He is still alive.
But this situation is indeed very rare.
That's great.
I'm curious how you found out.
Because of this key.
If he were really dead,
after rigor mortis,
the body would become very soft,
but I couldn't take this key out.
So I thought
maybe there was still a glimmer of hope.
It just so happens
that you are his first blood source.
Maybe you can wake him up.
But if we do this,
there will be a problem.
Ordinary maintenance doses
will be ineffective for him.
Only your blood will work.
Have you thought it through?
Of course.
After the blood transfusion,
I will take him to a lab in the UK.
The most precise instruments are there.
I'll have to trouble you to wait for news.
Okay.
Dad,
[Spirit Tablet of Lu Wenbiao]
don't worry.
I've taken care of everything in the gang.
I've turned several branches
into rehabilitation centers,
specializing in treating
the aftereffects of the poison.
By the way,
Uncle Zhong has been busy
doing business recently
and made a lot of money.
We took out half of it
and set up the Tianjiu Alley Fund.
All victims can receive subsidies
until they start a new life.
♪ As bells ring out, the old world falls ♪
I'm sorry,
Dad.
♪ Tear through the dark
to safeguard the dawn ♪
I couldn't be the son you wanted me to be.
♪ Chasing the light ♪
But I will never forget
♪ And breaking through disorientation ♪
♪ Against the wind, we forge
a brand‑new chapter ♪
to protect what truly
needs to be protected.
♪ Who prays with palms pressed together? ♪
♪ Who grants me
the strength of redemption? ♪
Dad,
♪ Faith ♪
I don't need your blessing.
♪ Is carved upon my chest ♪
♪ Bursting forth in blazing dawn light ♪
I can walk my own path.
♪ No more wandering down the road ahead ♪
♪ My steps are unstoppable ♪
But if possible,
♪ Side by side, we go for tomorrow ♪
♪ Marching toward a new battlefield ♪
I beg you
♪ Behold the sinking sun
at the abyss's end ♪
to bless another person.
♪ A faint flicker of firelight ♪
♪ Stubbornly illuminates
the endless night ♪
Please.
♪ Like the last glimmer of hope ♪
♪ An undying faith ♪
♪ Against towering waves ♪
♪ I chase the direction
of the dawn break ♪
[One year later]
Mr. Lu,
I'm very sorry to inform you
that Mr. Shen's cerebral condition
has deteriorated severely,
and his illness is beyond our control.
Please accept our deepest condolences.
Mr. Shen specifically asked us
not to tell you,
but his remains have already
been transferred back to Ningcheng.
[Ningcheng Train Station]
Officer Shen,
you've made progress.
You finally tricked me once.
What are you going to say this time?
Hello
or goodbye?
Long time no see.
[The End]